Suddenly, my mother came home and
said that the little one was still not feeling well. When my mother
arrived, all of us had gone to work in the field
.  Since my mother doesn't
eat non-veg on Sunday, I wanted to have something else. I didn't have
anything else at home, so I thought I'd make something with some bread
crumbs. I didn't have
time to watch it on YouTube, so I simply
made a double comet that came to me.  My mother would eat a little bit of food. I would
pack some for all of us and stay overnight. I won't be leaving tomorrow morning. I don't know. There are still a few
days left. I
can't stay at anyone's house for the night. But somehow the evening has already
passed. I said, "I'll cook while I'm here or the kids will make a fuss over you later." No one else understood me like a mother understands her children. I don't like to tell anyone to do anything, but even if my mother says no, she won't go.  And when all the
work is done, Mom
goes home.